The last intersection still counts the hours
마지막 교차로는 아직도 시간을 헤아리네.
Red yellow green for empty towers
텅 빈 빌딩들을 위한 빨강 노랑 초록.
Concrete veins where nothing flows
아무것도 흐르지 않는 콘크리트 혈관.
A faithful machine that never knows
결코 알지 못하는 충실한 기계.
Still changing colors for no one there
아무도 없는데도 여전히 색을 바꾸네.
A signal thrown into the air
허공에 던져진 신호.
No hand to stop no wheel to turn
멈출 손도, 돌릴 바퀴도 없어.
It keeps on burning just to burn
그저 불타기 위해 계속 불타오르네.
The paint is peeling off the lanes
차선 위 페인트는 벗겨지고.
The crosswalk faded by the rains
빗물에 바랜 횡단보도.
But every thirty seconds sharp
하지만 정확히 30초마다.
It shifts its light like a beating heart
뛰는 심장처럼 불빛을 바꾸네.
Still changing colors for no one there
아무도 없는데도 여전히 색을 바꾸네.
A signal thrown into the air
허공에 던져진 신호.
No hand to stop no wheel to turn
멈출 손도, 돌릴 바퀴도 없어.
It keeps on burning just to burn
그저 불타기 위해 계속 불타오르네.
Still changing colors for no one there
아무도 없는데도 여전히 색을 바꾸네.
A signal thrown into the air
허공에 던져진 신호.
No hand to stop no wheel to turn
멈출 손도, 돌릴 바퀴도 없어.
It keeps on burning just to burn
그저 불타기 위해 계속 불타오르네.